OPEN CUPBOARD
GET PLASTIC BOWL
CLOSE CUPBOARD
PUT BOWL
OPEN CUPBOARD
GET FLOUR
GET YEAST
PUT YEAST
PUT FLOUR
GET SALT
GET OIL
PUT SALT
PUT OLIVE OIL
PICK OLIVE OIL
search for another olive oil
open olive oil
remove cover from olive oil bottle
open trash can
throw cover
close trash can
open drawer
get two spoons
get three spoons
close drawer
get sugar
put sugar
pick up kettle
open kettle
open tap
hold kettle and fill kettle with water
close tap
close kettle
put kettle
switch kettle on
Open cupboard
Get two glasses
Close cupboard
Put one glass inside bowel
Put one glass down
Pick up flour
Open flour
Pour flour into cup
Empty flour cup into bowel
Put cup
Put flour into cup
Pour flower into cup
Pick cup
Empty flour into bowel
Put cup down
Close flour
put flour down
pick up spoon
open sugar jar
scoop sugar
put one spoon two spoons of sugar into bowl
put sugar jar
close sugar jar
put spoon
pick up salt
pick up spoon
pour salt into spoon
empty spoon in bowl
put salt
put spoon
pick up yeast
read yeast recipe
open yeast
open yeast can
open trash bin
throw can cover
close trash bin
pick up spoon
scoop yeast
put yeast in bowl
mix flour and yeast in bowl using spoon
mix flour
pick up olive oil
pick up spoon
put spoon
open olive oil bottle
remove cap from olive oil bottle
open trash bin
throw cap
close trash bin
pick up olive oil
pour olive oil in spoon
pour spoon
pour olive oil
pickup glass
pickup kettle
enter tea water into glass
fill glass
put glass
wait for kettle
waiting for kettle to boil
still waiting for kettle to boil
hold kettle
pickup kettle
pour hot water in glass from kettle
put kettle down
pick up glass
pour the water into bowl
put glass down
mix bowl
mix mixture into bowl
mix mixture in bowl using spoon
still mixing mixture
remove remainder of mixture from spoon
mix mixture using hand
mixing mixture using hand
open flour
get extra flour using hand
mix mixture using hand
still mixing mixture using hand and bowl
still mixing dough
pick up flour with left hand
add flour to mix
and continue mixing
mix mixture using hand and bowl
Pick up olive oil
Add olive to bowl
Pick up mixture
Form mixture into bowl
Add olive oil
Form mixture using two hands into bowl
Pick up mixture
Spread olive oil
Add olive oil to surface
Form bowl from mixture
put mixture back into bowl
pickup olive oil
pour olive oil into hand
spread olive oil on top of mixture
clear hand
pickup mixture from bowl
put down mixture into bowl
clear hand
still clearing hand
open tap
wash hands
Still washing hands
Pickup washing liquid
Pour washing liquid into hand
Washing hands
Close tap
Pickup towel
Dry hands
Open drawer
Get towel
Search towel
Close drawer
Cover bowl using towel
Move yeast can
Pickup bowl
open oven
pull drawer
return drawer
put bowl into oven
push drawer
close oven
set timer
open fridge
get meat
put down meat
pick up pan
put pan
pick up chopping board
pick up knife
put chopping board and knife
pick up two spoons
close olive oil bottle
move olive oil bottle
pickup two glasses
put glasses and spoon next to sink
close flour
pick up flour
pick up salt
put salt
open cupboard
put flour
close cupboard
pick up can yeast
close can yeast
pick up sugar jar
put sugar jar
open cupboard
put can yeast
close cupboards
pick up sponge
Open tap
Clean surface
Open trash bin
Open tap
Pour liquid into hand
Wash hands
Close tap
Pick up towel
Dry hands
Pick up chopping board
Put chopping board
Pick up onion
Put onion on chopping board
Chop end of onion
peel onion
still peeling onion
peeling onion
put onion
pick up chopping board
open trash
throw peels
close trash bin
put chopping board
put onion on chopping board
slice onion using knife
still slicing onion
chopping onion
chop onion
still chopping onion
remove remaining slices
pickup remaining slices
open trash
throw remaining slices
close trash
pickup slice
open trash bin
throw slice
pickup chopping board
move chopping board
pickup knife
remove meat packaging
cut meat packaging
pick up knife
cut meat
still cutting meat
remove packaging
open trash bin
throw cover
close trash bin
pick up oil
open oil
pour oil into pan
while holding oil switch on stove
shake oil bottle
close oil bottle
open trash bin
throw oil bottle
open drawer
pick up wooden spoon
close drawer
waiting for oil to heat
pick up chopping board
pour onion into pan
poring onion pieces using wooden stick
Put chopping board
Stir onion in pan
Still stiring onions
Hold pan and
Stir onion
Open ventilator
Open cupboard
Get garlic
Get pepper
Get herb
Searching for paprika
Get paprika
stir onion using wooden spoon
still stirring onion
close cupboard
stir onion
hold pan and stir onion
put wooden spoon
pickup wooden spoon
stir onion
hold pan and stir onion
pickup garlic
open garlic
pour garlic into pan
put garlic down
Stir onion and garlic in pan using wooden spoon
Hold pan and
Stir onion
Move knife
Pick meat
Put meat into pan
Break meat into pieces and
Put meat in pan
Pick up meat
Break meat into pieces and
Put meat in pan
Pick up spoon
Stir meat
pick up meat
break meat into pieces
add to pan
pick up meat
break meat into pieces
add to pan
pick up meat
break meat into pieces
and add to pan
pick up spoon
mix meat
hold pan and mix meat
lower heat
pick up meat
break meat into pieces
add meat to pan
pick up meat
hold pan and mix meat with onions using wooden spoon
break meat in pan
mix meat in pan using wooden spoon
turn meat in pan
turning meat in pan
break meant in pan using wooden spoon
Turning meat in pan
Break meat in pan using wooden spoon
Turn meat
Stir meat
Break meat
Turn meat
turn meat
holding pan and turning meat
lower heat
pickup spoon
break meat
turn meat
stir meat
move spoon
pickup lid
cover pan
pickup packaging
open trash bin
throw package
close trash bin
open fridge
get stock
put stock
open chicken stock
open cupboard
get glass
put glass
put stock into glass
close ventilator
pick up kettle
add hot water into glass
return kettle
open trash bin
throw
close cupboard
open drawer
get spoon
stir stock in glass
hold glass
stir
stock
hold glass and mix stock with hot water
stirring stock
carry glass and stir stock
return glass
hold glass and stir stock
still stirring stock remove spoon open lid
hold lid and pour stock into pan
put glass
pickup spoon
remove stock
put stock
Put spoon
Pick up wooden spoon
Stir meat water and hold lid
Hold lid and stir meat
Cover lid
Put spoon
Lower heat
Pick up plates
Open cupboard
Return plates
Put plates
Pick up plates
Pick up plate
Put plate
pick up tray
open cupboard
pull trays
put tray
close cupboard
pick up glass
open cupboard
put glass
pick up tongs
open drawer
put tongs
pick up cutlery
open drawer
put knife
put spoon
put forks
close drawer
wear gloves
empty sink
Pick up sponge
Put sponge
Hold sink and
Empty sink
Clean sink
Pick up sink hole
Open trash bin
Clean sink hole
Close trash bin
Return sink hole
Pick up liquid
Open tap
Fill liquid
Shake liquid
Spread liquid
Spread cleaning liquid
Put cleaning liquid
Pick up sponge
Clean sink
cleaning sink
still cleaning sink using sponge
open tap
wash sponge
put sponge
pick sponge
pick washing liquid
pour washing liquid
pick glass
wash glass
pick spoon
wash spoon
put spoon
pick glass
open tap
rinse glass
wash glass
pick knife
wash knife
pick glass
put glass
pick spoon
rinse spoon
wash spoon
pick glass
open tap
rinse glass
wash glass
put sponge
open tap
rinse glass
close tap
put glass
pickup knife
open tap
rinse knife
put knife
pickup spoon
rinse spoon
put spoon
pickup cutlery
rinse cutlery
put cutlery
pickup spoon
rinse spoon
put spoon
pickup glass
rinse glass
put glass
pick up glass
rinse glass
close tap
put glass
empty sink
hold in empty sink
remove glass
open lid
pick up wooden spoon
stir meat
put lid
hold pan and stir meat
breaking meat into smaller pieces
turning and stirring meat
turn meat
Turn meat
Stir meat
Still stiring meat using wooden spoon
Pick up herb
Pour pepper into cover
Pour pepper on meat
Pick herb
Pour herb
Close herb
Hold pan and
Stir meat
Pick up lid
Cover pan
Put spoon
Open cupboard
Pick up glass
Close cupboard
Pick up water filter
Hold glass and
Pour water into glass
Put water filter
Drink from glass
Put glass down
Pick up lid
Put lid
Stir meat
Increase heat
Hold pan and
Stir meat
put food on spoon
open drawer get fork
pick up a bit of meat using fork
taste meat
put fork
lower heat
pick up lid
put lid
set off timer
[END SUBTITLE]